tomorrow the house will votee to repeal
Obamacare so if you're thinking about
getting a life-threatening illness that
could bankrupt you and your family
today's the
day Republicans need 216 votes and only
have a margin of error of 21 votes which
is much smaller than three million vote
margin of error they needed to win the
election that is why Steve bennon sent
his assistant thric married Atlantic
City casino magnate and ex Pizza Hut
spokesman Donald Trump to convince
Republicans to take health insurance
away from millions of people also to
golf and permitting avoid his third wife
now back in Mordor DC house speaker and
sociopath Mickey Mouse Club member Paul
Ryan has been leading the effort and
enticing amendments to the new health
Bill to attract more Republican votes
because the thought of kicking 14
million people off their health
insurance just isn't doing it for him
anymore you guys so comedians what
amendments can they add to the American
Healthcare Act to make it more
attractive to
Republicans har healthc care is free to
anyone who agrees to be a slave okay all
right I'll give me points to that uh
Eugene um if you were diagnosed with an
STD Paul Ryan pushes you out of
window Craig uh some young boys in an
airport Rush trim all right
boys